<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Elo</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="sign_in_here"><u>Already a user? Sign In</u>.</string>
    <string name="register_here"><u>Hey there.. are you new to Elo?</u>.</string>

    <!-- Example General settings -->
    <string name="pref_header_general">General</string>

    <string name="pref_title_social_recommendations">Enable social recommendations</string>
    <string name="pref_description_social_recommendations">Recommendations for people to contact
        based on your message history
    </string>

    <string name="pref_title_display_name">Display name</string>
    <string name="pref_default_display_name">John Smith</string>

    <string name="pref_title_add_friends_to_messages">Add friends to messages</string>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_titles">
        <item>Always</item>
        <item>When possible</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example settings for Data & Sync -->
    <string name="pref_header_data_sync">Data &amp; sync</string>

    <string name="pref_title_sync_frequency">Sync frequency</string>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_titles">
        <item>15 minutes</item>
        <item>30 minutes</item>
        <item>1 hour</item>
        <item>3 hours</item>
        <item>6 hours</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_values">
        <item>15</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>60</item>
        <item>180</item>
        <item>360</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <string name="pref_title_system_sync_settings">System sync settings</string>

    <!-- Example settings for Notifications -->
    <string name="pref_header_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_new_message_notifications">New message notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_ringtone">Ringtone</string>
    <string name="pref_ringtone_silent">Silent</string>

    <string name="pref_title_vibrate">Vibrate</string>

    <string name="my_link">Copyright 2014 - 2017 Henning Dodenhof

Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
You may obtain a copy of the License at

    http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0

Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
limitations under the License.
</string>
    <string name="my_link_2">The MIT License (MIT)

Copyright (&#169;) 2016 Abdullaev Ozodrukh

Permission is hereby granted, free of charge, to any person obtaining a copy
of this software and associated documentation files (the "Software"), to deal
in the Software without restriction, including without limitation the rights
to use, copy, modify, merge, publish, distribute, sublicense, and/or sell
copies of the Software, and to permit persons to whom the Software is
furnished to do so, subject to the following conditions:

The above copyright notice and this permission notice shall be included in
all copies or substantial portions of the Software.

THE SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR
IMPLIED, INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY,
FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE
AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER
LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM,
OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER DEALINGS IN
THE SOFTWARE.</string>


    <string name="dummycontent"> The new $799 Mavic Air shares a lot of similarities with both the DJI Spark and the Mavic Pro and Pro Platinum. Like those models, it’s a compact drone with a 12-megapixel camera and a handful of different flying and shooting modes. It’s not targeted toward professionals, but rather hobbyists or enthusiasts who might be buying their first drone for aerial photography and videography and aren’t satisfied with the Spark’s limited creative options. The Air also has a couple of new tricks, like new obstacle avoidance technology. The new $799 Mavic Air shares a lot of similarities with both the DJI Spark and the Mavic Pro and Pro Platinum. Like those models, it’s a compact drone with a 12-megapixel camera and a handful of different flying and shooting modes. It’s not targeted toward professionals, but rather hobbyists or enthusiasts who might be buying their first drone for aerial photography and videography and aren’t satisfied with the Spark’s limited creative options. The Air also has a couple of new tricks, like new obstacle avoidance technology.</string>
</resources>
